

MOHAMAD ADNAN SAMIR ZAKZOUK

WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

- +20 1111 301 567
- ✓ adnansamir005@gmail.com
- Apt 9 /128 / Al-Salam Street / 6th of October city / Giza / Egypt
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/adnan-zakzouk-a46b73286/
- https://github.com/Commando-Adnan
- Be https://www.behance.net/abodbotho

EDUCATION

2022 - 2023 AL-MALIK AL-SALIH PUBLIC HIGHSCHOOL

highschool degree

SKILLS

- Project Management
- Critical thinking
- Attention to details
- Teamwork
- Effective Communication

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATES

- Meta Front-End Developer Meta
- Web Design for Everybody Coursera
- Motion foundation Ben Marriott
- leveraged editor course

LANGUAGES

- Arabic Native
- English B2
- German A1
- Azerbaijani A1

PROFILE

Dedicated and passionate web developer with diverse expertise and backgrounds. My skill set includes front-end web development, IT business startup consultation, project managment, motion graphic design, and animation.

proficient in teamwork, communication, and have an open-minded personality.

WORK EXPERIENCE

HY business

pre-incubation consultant

AUGUST 2024 - NOVEMBER 2024

- HY Business is a tech talent startup with partnerships in Germany and Switzerland, providing young IT talents from the MENA region, particularly those from underprivileged backgrounds with opportunities and training to travel abroad for professional internships and training in various IT fields.
- During my time with the pre-incubation team, I engaged in participating in sessions on marketing, finance, entrepreneurship, and IT business, led by esteemed professors like Dr. Aisha Hamdy.
- played a key role in creating a detailed market plan, specifying market segmentations, developing a talent framework, and matching candidates to hiring partners' needs.

TDH & UNHCR

NOVEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

community empowerment programme participant

- Attended the program for nearly three years, gaining extensive experience in multiple fields and pursuits.
- Earned professional certificates in front-End web development, motion graphic design, as well as academically accredited certificates in the field of healthcare and public health science.
- The program provided ample opportunities to connect with like-minded professionals and experts in the field of web development and IT. By participating in collaborative projects, and immensely valuable council and referrals throughout the way, I built a strong network of peers and mentors.

Motion Designer / Animator

Self Employed

JANUARY 2024 - JUNE 2024

- My skillset includes motion graphic animations, I always had a passion for motion graphics and animation, I
 developed this skill using the same strategies I used when learning web development, building a strong
 foundation and familiarising myself with the important software tools, then fortifying this knowledge with creating
 projects, for the knowledge part, I joined Ben Mariott's motion foundation course who is hailed by many as one of
 the best in the industry, and for the projects part I created multiple visually captivating projects that are available
 on my behance portfolio.
- I developed this skill is mainly to enhance my web applications and web projects, and I believe it is a great addition for me especially with my web development career aspirations.
- I aspire to use this skill to create visually appealing elements and interfaces, resulting in a more dynamic and interactive websites.

content writer and proofreader

SEPTEMBER 2024 - JANUARY 2023

the Egyptian Red Crescent

- Content Writing and Proofreading: worked as an Arabic/English content writer and proofreader within the Egyptian Red Crescent's media team, producing high-quality content for various platforms.
- Advanced Writing Skills: Worked with complex medical concepts, which significantly enhanced my writing skills
 and ability to convey intricate information clearly and accurately.
- Attention to Detail: Leveraged my acute attention to detail in proofreading tasks, further refining my writing and ensuring the accuracy and quality of all content produced.

project manager assistant

JANUARY 2024 - JULY 2021

Watan for Cultural and Social development

- Community Engagement: Worked on numerous projects that significantly benefited the local community.
- First 1,000 Days: participated in Facilitating the "First 1,000 Days" programme offered by the World Food Programme providing financial and medical support to pregnant and nursing women so they can meet their essential needs.
- other Projects: participated in managing other projects such as the clothing distribution program, COVID-19 awareness campaigns, online vaccine registration, and many others.